Welcome aboard, Dr. Cooper.
First time anyone said that to me in orbit.
I've been saying it for 25 years.
You're the first to answer.
Come closer.
Get her.
Every sunrise, every shadow, every pulse of light, I've watched it all from here.
25 years of storms, of silence, of hope.
Doesn't it get lonely?
Only if you forget what you're watching.
Sarah isn't just metal and memory.
She's the lens through which Earth learned to breathe again.
She mapped the droughts, tracked the wildfires, whispered to the oceans, measured the air
we once poisoned, and taught us how to heal it.
You talk about her like she's alive.
After a while, you stop saying circuits.
You start hearing a heartbeat.
She watched humanity look back and choose to care.
That's what Tara has done for us, Dr. She reminded us we're still one planet, still one
home.
And you stayed to witness it.
Someone had to remember.